firsttechfed.com 2012-05-11

# Privacy Policy

                          Privacy Policy
                                        WHAT DO FIRST TECH FEDERAL CREDIT UNION AND FIRST TECH
                 FACTS                  INSURANCE SERVICES DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?*
                                        Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit
         Why?                           some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share and protect your personal
                                        information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
                                        The types of personal information we collect and share depends on the product(s) or service(s) you have with us.
                                        This information can include:
         What?                            •   Social Security number and account transactions.
                                          •   Payment history and account balances.
                                          •   Credit history and checking account information.
                                        All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section
         How?                           below, we list the reasons financial companies share their customers’ personal information; the reasons First Tech
                                        Federal Credit Union and First Tech Insurance Services choose to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                                      Do First Tech Federal Credit
         Reasons we can share your personal information                             Union and First Tech Insurance            Can you limit this sharing?
                                                                                             Services share?
         For our everyday business purposes — such as to process your
         transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders                            Yes                                    No
         and legal investigations or report to credit bureaus.
         For our marketing purposes — to offer our products and services
                                                                                                    Yes                                    No
         to you.
         For joint marketing with other financial companies                                         Yes                                    Yes
         For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes — information
                                                                                                    Yes                                    No
         about your transactions and experiences.
         For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes — information
                                                                                                    No                               We don’t share
         about your creditworthiness.
         For our affiliates to market to you                                                        Yes                                    Yes
         For non-affiliates to market to you                                                       No**                             We don’t share**
                                          •   Visit firsttechfed.com and click on “Opt-Out” in the bottom navigation bar.
                                          •   Call our Member Service Center at 855.855.8805.
         To limit
                                        Please note: If you’re a new member, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we delivered
         our sharing                    this notice. When you’re no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
                                        However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
                                          •   Visit firsttechfed.com and click on “Opt-Out” in the bottom navigation bar.
         To limit our direct              •   Call our Member Service Center at 855.855.8805.
         marketing by email,
                                        Please note: We may contact our existing members by email, mail or telephone to offer additional financial products
         mail or phone                  or services that we believe may be of interest to you. You may direct us not to send you such offers.
         Questions?                     Call 855.855.8805 or visit firsttechfed.com.
         Who we are
         Who is providing this notice?                                  First Tech Federal Credit Union and First Tech Insurance Services.
Rev. 03.12                                                                                                                                                  Page 1

                          Privacy Policy
         What we do
                                                                         To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use
         How does First Tech Federal Credit Union and First Tech
                                                                         federally compliant security measures. These measures include computer safeguards
         Insurance Services protect my personal information?
                                                                         and secured files and buildings.
                                                                         We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
                                                                           •  Open an account or use your credit or debit card.
         How does First Tech Federal Credit Union and First Tech           •  Apply for a loan or give us your contact information.
         Insurance Services collect my personal information?               •  Make deposits or withdrawals from your account.
                                                                         We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates,
                                                                         or other companies.
                                                                         Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
                                                                           •  Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your
                                                                              creditworthiness.
         Why can’t I limit all sharing?
                                                                           •  Affiliates from using your information to market to you.
                                                                           •  Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you.
                                                                         State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
         What happens when I limit sharing for an account I
                                                                         Your choice will apply to everyone on your account.
         hold jointly with someone else?
         Definitions
                                                                         Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
         Affiliates
                                                                         nonfinancial companies.
                                                                         Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
         Nonaffiliates**
                                                                         nonfinancial companies.
                                                                         A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market
         Joint marketing
                                                                         financial products or services to you.
         Other important information
         You may have other privacy protections under applicable state laws. To the extent these state laws apply, we will comply with them when we
         share information about you.
         For California residents: In accordance with California law, we won’t share information we collect about you with companies outside of our
         corporate family, except as permitted by law, including, for example, with your consent or to service your account. We’ll limit sharing among our
         companies to the extent required by California law.
         For Nevada residents: We may contact our existing members by telephone to offer additional financial products that we believe may be of interest
         to you. You have the right to opt out of these calls by adding your name to our internal do-not-call list. To opt out of these calls, please call us at
         855.855.8805 or visit us online at firsttechfed.com and tell us your preference. We’re providing you this notice under Nevada state law. In addition to
         contacting us, Nevada residents can contact the Nevada Attorney General for more information about your opt out rights by calling 775.684.1100,
         emailing bcpinfo@ag.state.nv.us, or by writing to: Office of the Attorney General, Nevada Department of Justice, Bureau of Consumer Protection
         100 North Carson Street, Carson City, NV 89701-4717.
         For Vermont residents: In accordance with Vermont law, we won’t share information we collect about you with companies outside of our corporate
         family, except as permitted by law, including, for example with your consent or to service your account. We won’t share information about your
         creditworthiness, but we may share information about our transactions or experiences with you within our corporate family without your consent.
         *First Tech Federal Credit Union includes Addison Avenue Investment Services. First Tech Insurance Services is the business name of Addison
         Avenue Financial Partners, LLC.
         **Please keep in mind that, as permitted by law, we share information about you with nonaffiliated third parties for our everyday business
         purposes and with nonaffiliated financial companies to jointly market financial products and services to you.
Rev. 03.12                                                                                                                                                          Page 2
